A warm home where I can stay out of the rain.
And now I've got a fluffy mattress...
Candy in the bottle, too.
Somehow I feel so satisfied.
You shouldn't feel satisfied just having one or two!
At that rate it'll take you 100 years to fill the bottle!
That's fine, Ioryogi.
Even if it takes 100 years, I'll try my best!
You think I'll put up with you for 100 years?
What shall I do?
Even the obvious things are always so hard
I just want to grin when I'm happy, sing when I'm in love
They say my dreams will come true someday
but when will someday come? I can't wait!
Count one, two, three and spread my arms
Gather the light to myself
Where is it? Tell me what I can do
Even if I'm hurt so much, even if I run so hard
Even if I collapse crying over and over, I still
believe in my amazing future
... Pulsing leaves.
You understand what you need to do, right?
Yes!
Heal scarred hearts, and collect candy.
The birdies are singing.
The morning dew glints off the flowers.
It smells great.
You see so much when you wake up early.
Going for a walk softening you up?
No way!
Oh, what a wonderful path!
She's so pretty.
Excuse me!
You saw?
Why are you crying?
Why?
Because... the foliage is so pretty.
You cry because the foliage is pretty?
You don't get it, do you?
I'm sorry.
By the way, who are you?
I'm Hanato Kobato.
I'm Kohaku.
Kohaku?
Ioryogi, you've got to keep pretending you're a stuffed animal.
Kohaku, Kohaku from Heaven?
Heaven?
Yes.
You smelled different than the other passersby.
Who is this?
Ioryogi.
It's okay in front of her.
Really?
Ioryogi? I've heard that name somewhere.
I can't remember.
Didn't I tell you!? Not Ioryogi, a name just like it.
A name just like it?
Perhaps you're Iorogi?
Yeah.
You two know each other?
Just by name.
I didn't expect the  Iorogi to be this cute.
Nah, this body is just...
I'm going by Ioryogi for now.
Understood.
Ioryogi, then.
And you're Kobato.
Yes!
I've got to finish watering the trees in the garden before the sunlight gets too strong.
Excuse me.
Sure.
What are you doing?
Oh, you scared me.
I'm looking at the leaves.
No matter how long I look, I can't cry.
I wonder why?
I dunno. But looking at them makes me want to cry.
Really? Tell me why.
The guy who was supposed to help is slacking off, so I'm gonna be picking them up all day. That makes me want to cry.
I'll do it! I'll get it done in a flash!
I'll help out, silly.
Kobato!
I'll help too!
Thank you.
What are you doing?
I want to know why Kohaku was crying.
If I find out, then maybe I can heal her.
I don't think you'll get it just looking at those...
But maybe I'll get some kind of hint.
I don't get it.
Figured.
All right, I guess I have to wake up early and go ask Kohaku again.
I overslept!
Saw that coming.
She's not here.
Welcome back.
I see you worked hard today.
It's Kohaku!
Wait!
Why?
Don't be such a wet rag.
A wet rag?
You'd just get in the way if you showed up now.
You can just wait at home rather than tracking me down in the street.
But walking home with you like this makes me happy.
Plus it lets me be with you a little longer.
Man, they're flirty.
Such a wonderful house.
You'll never have one like it.
You're not even supposed to be here.
Rich doesn't mean her heart works different from everyone else's.
Where'd you get that one from?
By reading the magazines at the convenience store!
Ioryogi?
Yeah?
When should I approach her?
That's not the problem.
Sorry I couldn't keep our appointment today.
You just pulled an all-nighter, so...
Plus, your patients are the most important thing.
You're important too.
I knew it. We're not supposed to be here, Kobato. Let's go home.
O spirit which sleeps within water, heed my call.
Rain down over the trees, giving your strength,
and gather to save those lives.
Fall, o rain of blessings!
It's so pretty.
Kobato?
Ioryogi?
I'm friggin' soaked now!
I'm so sorry!
Really, I'm sorry.
Don't worry. Sorry for just coming in uninvited.
Why are you here?
To be honest...
I saw you with a man yesterday.
Sorry for following you.
I didn't know why you cried.
And I was really curious.
I don't really understand it myself.
But when I see something beautiful I want to show it to Shuichiro.
It reminds me of him.
Oh.
When I think of Shuichiro, I...
When you think of him?
My heart aches...
It aches?
It makes me feel gloomy.
Remembering how satisfied I feel when I'm by his side.
Remembering that shy smile of his.
All those memories wash over me.
Like this?
I start crying just like that.
I don't get it.
I'm sorry, I can't explain it very well.
So love makes you miserable, makes you want to cry!?
Love?
Love, huh.
I see, it's love.
And here you said you didn't get it.
The magazines said that love makes you worry.
Are you having any problems, Kohaku?
Well...
Yes?
The problem is that Shuichiro is always so busy.
We've never even gone on a date.
A date?
It's when you go with someone you like to an amusement park or something.
It'd make me so happy...
A date at an amusement park?
Leave it to me, Kohaku!
I'll try my best!
If she can go with Shuichiro to an amusement park,
Kohaku's heart will be healed.
First, I've got to check out parks!
So this is an amusement park.
It looks so fun.
Tickets are ￥3,000!?
Wow, amusement parks are pricy.
But I'm broke.
What should I do?
Don't ask me!
Maybe you should focus on actually healing Kohaku.
Oh, Ioryogi!
First prize, a trip to Hawaii!
Second prize, an onsen vacation!
Third prize, amusement park tickets!
Spin the handle, and see what color ball you get!
All prizes are for two!
Step right up to the lotto!
Wonderful! It looks like they're giving away tickets to that amusement park!
Here you go.
Where's your ticket, young lady?
If you don't have a ticket you can't play.
So I need a lotto ticket before I can get an amusement park ticket...
A lotto ticket...
You can't be depressed about it forever.
You've got to remember Kohaku.
I can't calm down about the ticket!
What are you so disappointed for?
Man, there's no way one would just drop out of the-
A lotto ticket!
Here's my lotto ticket!
Let me spin it!
Here you go!
Go ahead.
I'll try my best!
I hope I get a ticket...
Congratulations, you win!
Really? I got something?
Really?
Fifth prize! A stuffed crocodile!
Take good care of it.
That's just a booby prize!
Why didn't you turn it down!?
It's rude to turn down something given so kindly.
But I need amusement park tickets.
Sorry...
Fujimoto!
You again?
Quit zoning out!
Are you delivering newspapers?
Yeah.
But Miss Sayaka said you delivered pizza.
Yeah, I do that too.
You have that many jobs?
What's that?
A crocodile I won.
But it's not what I really needed.
Amusement park tickets?
Yeah, I got them at work.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Can I have these tickets?
Are you that stupid?
How about if I trade you the crocodile?
No way. I don't even need it.
Please!
Then Kohaku will be able to go on a date there.
Here.
Now Shuichiro will go on a date with you.
Just do whatever.
What's with those newspapers?
I'm helping deliver them.
You're delivering newspapers to get those tickets?
Yeah. Here.
Thank you. But I can't take them.
Why?
Shuichiro is so busy that we'd never get the chance to use them.
You worked so hard for them that I don't want them to go to waste...
That's it! Kobato, you go!
Me?
Yeah, take Ioryogi.
Take Ioryogi?
Don't even think about it!
No way! You've got to go with Shuichiro!
But I don't think I'll be able to.
And I don't want to be selfish.
That's...
Is it selfish?
When Shuichiro is with you, he seems so happy.
I'm sure you're as dear to him as he is to you.
I know he'll go on the date.
Kobato...
Shuichiro.
Can I have those tickets?
Of course! Here you go!
Shuichiro... Can we go together?
I don't mind ferris wheels.
I can't see them anymore.
Of course! Let's go home.
Okay...
I'm sure they're having fun.
I guess.
Bunny?
He's a messenger from Heaven.
Heaven? Another friend of yours?
A time limit?
How long?
Having to fill the bottle before the four seasons pass, huh?
You heard, right?
Yeah, about the time limit.
I've got four seasons, then?
Meaning you need to fill the bottle within a year.
If you don't...
I'll never be able to go to that place.
So, what's in there?
There aren't any more.
Do you understand why?
I don't.
Didn't I heal Kohaku?
Before that. People who're already happy don't need to be healed.
Meaning she wasn't hurt.
That's nothing to be glad about!
100 points!
100 points?
Minus!
Minus 100 points?
You picked the wrong person. That's enough for someone who can't understand that.
But I'm glad I made her so happy!
Don't be so optimistic!
You've got one year! Get to work!
Okay! I'll try my best!
Stop making that face!
I'm not!
I told you to get to work!
What kind of face should I make when I get to work?
Like this, if you can do it.
People all want to fly
but they're cheated by gravity
everyone can really fly
She must be so unhappy because
she forgot her own shadow somewhere
Then...
If you tell me "thanks", if you say "thanks" and smile
Going back and forth, we'll be happy
You'll be happy, there'll be nothing to worry about
As long as we're together
It's strange, I'm crying even though I'm happy
... Hotaru's promise.
Next episode